BARBARA MORGAN

3306 Choir St, Dallas, Texas 75237 Cell: 682-622-1873 - bhenry6943@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Efficient and reliable CNA with 18 years experience and 7 years experience in a hospital setting. Assisted with technical nursing treatments, supported diagnostic procedures and charted resident records. Interested in a full-time role as a nursing assistant in a top-notch healthcare

SKILLS

- CPR/First Aid certified
- Patient-focused care
- Companionship and emotional support
- Compassionate
- Efficient and reliable team player
- Adaptable

- Feeding assistance expert
- Dementia and Alzheimer's knowledge
- Trustworthy companion
- Committed team player

WORK HISTORY

10/2012 to Current Patient Care Technician / Unit Secretary

Baylor Scott & White Medical Center-Sunnyvale - Sunnyvale, Texas

- Maintained accurate records of patient care, condition, progress and concerns.
- Monitored vital signs, such as blood pressure and pulse.
- Tested and recorded blood glucose levels.
- Obtained information about clients' medical history, drug history, complaints and allergies.
- Assisted patients with bathing, oral hygiene, grooming, feeding and elimination.
- Performed clerical duties, such as word processing, data entry, answering phones and filing.

09/2014 to 05/2017 Patient Care Technician

Select Specialty Hospital – Dallas, Texas

- Answered patient calls for care and feeding.
- Collects patient specimens and data, including vital signs, input/output and other delegated measurements.
- Answered call lights and aided in patient comfort and safety by adjusting beds, lights, bed rails, pillows, patients' clothing and bedside tables/equipment.
- Performed direct patient care aimed at increasing comfort, psycho, social and spiritual well-being by providing assistance with personal hygiene, physical comfort, nutrition, elimination, prevention of skin breakdown, rehabilitation and safety.
- Documents objective data and routine aspects of patient care.

03/2012 to 10/2012 Certified Nurse Assistance

Kindred Healthcare Rehabilitation – Grapevine, Texas

- Answered call lights and aided in patient comfort and safety by adjusting beds, lights, bed rails, pillows, patients' clothing and bedside tables/equipment.
- Performed direct patient care aimed at increasing comfort, psycho, social and spiritual well-being by providing assistance with personal hygiene, physical comfort, nutrition, elimination, prevention of skin breakdown, rehabilitation and safety.
- Assisted patients with bathing, oral hygiene, grooming, feeding and elimination.
- Assisted with patient transfer and ambulation.
- Monitored vital signs, such as blood pressure and pulse.

EDUCATION

2016

High School Diploma:

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Nurses AideBCLS Certification